<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>&#43;आरण्यकम् on साम-वेदे विश्वासटिप्पन्यः</title>
    <link>https://vishvAsa.github.io/vedAH_sAma/jaiminIyam/AraNyakam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in &#43;आरण्यकम् on साम-वेदे विश्वासटिप्पन्यः</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://vishvAsa.github.io/vedAH_sAma/jaiminIyam/AraNyakam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Oertel en</title>
      <link>https://vishvAsa.github.io/vedAH_sAma/jaiminIyam/AraNyakam/oertel_en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vishvAsa.github.io/vedAH_sAma/jaiminIyam/AraNyakam/oertel_en/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Jaiminiya or Talavakara Upanisad Brahmana&#xA;Hanns Oertel, Journal of the American Oriental Society, Vol. 16 (1896), 79-260&#xA;ARTICLE IV.&#xA;THE JAIMINIYA OR TALAVAKĀRA UPANISAD BRAHMANA:&#xA;TEXT, TRANSLATION, AND NOTES.&#xA;BY HANNS OERTEL, PH.D.,&#xA;INSTRUCTOR IN YALE UNIVERSITY.&#xA;Presented to the Society April, 1893.&#xA;INTRODUCTION.&#xA;THE text of the Brāhmaṇa, as here published, is founded on manuscript material sent by A. C. Burnell* in 1881 to Professor Whitney (see Proc. A.O.Š. for May, 1883; Journ. vol. xi., p. cxliv), as follows:&#xA;A., according to Burnell&amp;rsquo;s note on the cover, copied &amp;ldquo;from a Malabar MS.&amp;rdquo; in 1878; at the end he has added: &amp;ldquo;Date of original, Kullam 1040-1864 A.D. From a MS. at Palghat&amp;rdquo;;&#xA;B., from &amp;ldquo;a MS. on talipot leaves, written about 300 years ago, and got from Tinnevelly, but which was originally brought from near Aleppee;&amp;rdquo; of this only the various readings are given, interlined in red ink on A.;&#xA;C., a transliterated text in Burnell&amp;rsquo;s own hand, breaking off after the beginning of i. 59, apparently because the copying was carried no further.&#xA;The text of A. and the variants from B. are in the Grantha character, on European paper. They were copied in transliteration by Professor John Avery, and the copy was compared with its originals by Professor Whitney, who also added the readings of C.; from this copy was prepared the text given below. The originals are now in the Library of the India Office, London.&#xA;The attempt has been made to obtain new materials, but without success. Professor G. Oppert, in his List of Sanskrit&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
